Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 2
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 2
- Box: 5, Folder: 10 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Item 2: The Gaffer, Publication (Box 5, Folder 10)
    By Corning Glass Works. May. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The Gaffer, Publication (Box 5, Folder 10)
    By Corning Glass Works. July. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Key to the Office, Publication (Box 5, Folder 10)
    By Corning Glass Works. Jan. Item is in English.
- Box: 5, Folder: 11 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Employee Magazine Ideas, Publication (Box 5, Folder 11)
    By Corn Products Company. Item is in English.
- Box: 5, Folder: 12 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Constitution and By-Laws, Publication (Box 5, Folder 12)
    By Corrective Officers Benevolent Association, Inc. Item is in English.
- Box: 5, Folder: 13 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: A Case Study in Labour Force Recruitment and Training, Publication (Box 5, Folder 13)
    By Cosmos Imperial Mills. Item is in English.
- Box: 5, Folder: 14 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: It Depends on Consumer Competence Whether Competition Improves Quality or Debases It, Publication (Box 5, Folder 14)
    By John Maurice clark. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Newsletter, Publication (Box 5, Folder 14)
    By Council on Consumer Information. Vol. 15, No. 2 Oct. Item is in English.
- Box: 5, Folder: 15 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: The Meaning of the Council for Financial Aid to Education, Inc., Publication (Box 5, Folder 15)
    By Council for Financial Aid to Education. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Education is Everybody's Business, Publication (Box 5, Folder 15)
    By Frank W. Abrams. Item is in English.
- Box: 5, Folder: 16 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Constitution and By-Laws of the Council of Profit Sharing Industries, Publication (Box 5, Folder 16)
    By Council of Profit Sharing Industries. Item is in English.
- Box: 5, Folder: 17 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Commmunications Materials Available to You as a Member of Council of Profit Sharing Industries, Publication (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Box: 5, Folder: 18 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Membership Roster, Publication (Box 5, Folder 18)
    By Council of Profit Sharing Industries. Aug. 31. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Profit Sharing, Publication (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Item 3: Roster Supplement, Publication (Box 5, Folder 18)
    By Council of Profit Sharing Industries. Sept. 1, 1964- March 31, 1965. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Membership Roster, Publication (Box 5, Folder 18)
    By Council of Profit Sharing Industries. June 1. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Membreship Roster, Publication (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Item 6: Scope and Activities of the Council of Profit Sharing Industries, Publication (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Item 7: Sixth Annual Conference Program, Publication (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Item 8: Union Leader Corporation, Publication (Box 5, Folder 18)
    By William Loeb. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Fifth Annual Conference Program, Publication (Box 5, Folder 18)
    By Council of Profit Sharing Industries. Nov. 6-7. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Seventh Annual Conference Program, Publication (Box 5, Folder 18)
    By Council of Profit Sharing Industries. Oct. 28-29. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Declaratin of Principles and Constitution, Publication (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Item 12: Membership, Publication (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Item 13: Membership List, Publication (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Item 14: Membership List, Publication (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Item 15: Membership List, Publication (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Item 16: Report to the Membership on the State of our Council, Publication (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Item 17: Council of Profit Sharing Industries Letter, Publication (Box 5, Folder 18)
    By Council of Profit Sharing Industries. Nov. 11. Item is in English.
- Box: 5, Folder: 19 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: The Senior Citizen, Publication (Box 5, Folder 19)
    By Council of Senior Citizens of Tompkins County. Feb. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Senior Citizen, Publication (Box 5, Folder 19)
    By Council of Senior Citizens of Tompkins County. Aug. Item is in English.
- Box: 5, Folder: 20 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Social Action: Church-Labor Relations, Publication (Box 5, Folder 20)
    By Council for Social Action of the Congregational Christian Church. Oct. 15, 1944. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Guiding Principles for Organized Labor and Management Relatinos, Publication (Box 5, Folder 20)
    By Council for Social Action of the Congregational Christian Church. Jan. Item is in English.
- Box: 5, Folder: 21 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: The Legend of Packing, Publication (Box 5, Folder 21)
    By Crandall Packing Company. Item is in English.
- Box: 5, Folder: 22 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Suggestion System, Publication (Box 5, Folder 22)
    By Crane Company. Item is in English.
- Box: 5, Folder: 23 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Record, Publication (Box 5, Folder 23)
    By Craddock Terry Shoe Corp. Aug. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Record, Publication (Box 5, Folder 23)
    By Craddock Terry Shoe Corp. Sept. Item is in English.
- Box: 5, Folder: 24 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Crane World, Publication (Box 5, Folder 24)
    By Crane Co. March. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Group Insurance for Our Employees, Publication (Box 5, Folder 24)
    By Crane Co. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Pension Plan, Publication (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Item 4: How the Crane Companies' Pension Plan, Publication (Box 5, Folder 24)
    By Crane Co. Oct. 1. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Chicago Works, Publication (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Item 6: Rules and Regulations, Publication (Box 5, Folder 24)
    By Crane Co. Aug. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Bulletin of Wages, Publication (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Item 8: CC Welcomes to Crane Co., Publication (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Item 9: Centennial Crane World Issue, Publication (Box 5, Folder 24)
    By Crane Co. July. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: How to Promote a Know-Your-Company Contest, Publication (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Item 11: Crane World, Publication (Box 5, Folder 24)
    By Crane Co. Dec. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Suggestin System, Publication (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Item 13: Annual Report, Publication (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Box: 5, Folder: 25 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: A Request From the Creative Problem-Solving Institute, Publication (Box 5, Folder 25)
    By Creative Education Foundation. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The 10th Annual Creative Problem-Solving Institute, Publication (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Item 3: Developments in the Creative Education Movement, Publication (Box 5, Folder 25)
    By Alex F. Osborn. Item is in English.
- Box: 5, Folder: 26 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Report of Proceedings, Publication (Box 5, Folder 26)
    By Creative Problem-Solving Institute-University of Buffalo. June 25-27. Item is in English.
- Box: 5, Folder: 27 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: The Credit Union Way, Publication (Box 5, Folder 27)
    By Credit Union National Association. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Credit Unions in Educational Groups, Publication (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Item 3: They Endorse All Credit Unions, Publication (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Item 4: The Credit Union Yearbook, Publication (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Item 5: The Credit Union Yearbook, Publication (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Item 6: Bibliography, Publication (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Item 7: What Are Credit Unions and How Can We Use Them, Publication (Box 5, Folder 27)
- Box: 5, Folder: 28 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: The Credit Union Yearbook, Publication (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Item 2: International Credit Union Yearbook, Publication (Box 5, Folder 28)
- Box: 5, Folder: 29 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: A Guide to Your Employee Benefits, Publication (Box 5, Folder 29)
    By Creole Petroleum Corporation. Item is in English.
- Box: 5, Folder: 30 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Wage and Salary: Training Course for Supervisors, Publication (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Item 2: Annual Report, Publication (Box 5, Folder 30)
- Box: 5, Folder: 31 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: Organization and Planning, Publication (Box 5, Folder 31)
    By Cresap, McCormick & Paget. Item is in English.
- Box: 5, Folder: 32 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: Introduction to Crocker-Anglo Bank, Publication (Box 5, Folder 32)
    By Crocker-Anglo Bank. Item is in English.
- Box: 5, Folder: 33 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: That You May Always Remember Crossett, Publication (Box 5, Folder 33)
    By Crosset Co. Item is in English.
- Box: 5, Folder: 34 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: Steps to Settling a Grievance, Publication (Box 5, Folder 34)
    By Crouse Hinds Company. 2 copies. Item is in English.
- Box: 5, Folder: 35 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: Bulletin 2591, Publication (Box 5, Folder 35)
    By Crouse Hinds Company. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Spans Four Fields in the Electrical Industry, Publication (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Item 3: Family Circle: Organization Charts of the Crouse-Hinds Company, Publication (Box 5, Folder 35)
    By Crouse Hinds Company. Jan. Item is in English.
- Box: 5, Folder: 36 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: News, Publication (Box 5, Folder 36)
    By Crouse Hinds Company. May-June. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: News, Publication (Box 5, Folder 36)
    By Crouse Hinds Company. March-April. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: News, Publication (Box 5, Folder 36)
    By Crouse Hinds Company. Jan.-Feb. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: News, Publication (Box 5, Folder 36)
    By Crouse Hinds Company. Nov.-Dec. Item is in English.
- Box: 5, Folder: 37 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Item 1: Welcome, Publication (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Item 2: You and Crouse-Hinds, Publication (Box 5, Folder 37)
- Box: 5, Folder: 38 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Item 1: Major Medical Insurance, Publication (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Item 2: Group Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Item 3: Take a Look at tomorrow with the Crouse Hinds Retirement Income Plan, Publication (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Item 4: Retirement Income Plan of Crouse Hinds Company, Publication (Box 5, Folder 38)
- Box: 5, Folder: 39 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Item 1: Principles of Personnel Administration, Publication (Box 5, Folder 39)
    By Anaconda Wire and Cable Company. March 7. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Service Award Plan, Publication (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Item 3: So you're Going to Move, Publication (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Item 4: So you're Going to Move: For Married Employees, Publication (Box 5, Folder 39)
- Box: 5, Folder: 40 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Item 1: Employee Security Program, Publication (Box 5, Folder 40)
    By Crown Central Petroleum Corporation. Item is in English.
- Box: 5, Folder: 41 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Item 1: Employees' Annual Report, Publication (Box 5, Folder 41)
    By Crown Cork and Seal Company, Inc. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Annual Report, Publication (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Item 3: The Crown Corker, Publication (Box 5, Folder 41)
    By Crown Cork and Seal Company, Inc. Sept. Item is in English.
- Box: 5, Folder: 42 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Item 1: Crown's Diamond Anniversary, Publication (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Item 2: Group Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Item 3: Your Retirement Income Plan, Publication (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Item 4: Wage and Salary Administratin Handbook, Publication (Box 5, Folder 42)
- Box: 5, Folder: 43 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Item 1: Your Suggestion Plan, Publication (Box 5, Folder 43)
    By Crown Zellerbach Corp. Item is in English.
- Box: 5, Folder: 44 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Item 1: Pulp, Paper and Pioneers-The Story of Crown Zellerbach Corp., Publication (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Item 2: Profile: Crown Zellerbach, Publication (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Item 3: Pulp, Paper and Pioneers, Publication (Box 5, Folder 44)
    By R.O. Hunt. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Growing Paper on Tree Farms, Publication (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Item 5: Years of Paper, Publication (Box 5, Folder 44)
    By Crown Zellerbach Corp. May. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Papermaking at Antioch, Publication (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Item 7: Crown Zellerbach Building, Publication (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Item 8: Partners in Industry, Publication (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Item 9: Job Introduction for New Employee, Publication (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Item 10: You and Your Retirement Plan, Publication (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Item 11: Rules and Customs, Publication (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Item 12: You and Your Welfare Plan, Publication (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Item 13: Retirement Plan, Publication (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Item 14: Retirement Plan, Publication (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Item 15: Retirement Plan/Annual Report, Publication (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Item 16: A Plan of Group Insurance for Salaried Employees, Publication (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Item 17: A Plan of Group Insurance for Hourly Employees, Publication (Box 5, Folder 44)
- Box: 5, Folder: 45 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Item 1: Management Digest, Publication (Box 5, Folder 45)
    By Crown Zellerbach Corp. Number 87 June 20. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Management Digest, Publication (Box 5, Folder 45)
    By Crown Zellerbach Corp. Number 89 July 30. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Management Digest, Publication (Box 5, Folder 45)
    By Crown Zellerbach Corp. Number 91 Aug. 16. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Management Digest, Publication (Box 5, Folder 45)
    By Crown Zellerbach Corp. Number 109 May 16. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Management Digest, Publication (Box 5, Folder 45)
    By Crown Zellerbach Corp. Number 113 July 22. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Management Digest, Publication (Box 5, Folder 45)
    By Crown Zellerbach Corp. Number 126. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Crown Zellerbach Times, Publication (Box 5, Folder 45)
    By Crown Zellerbach Corp. Vol. 2, No. 3 March. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Crown Zellerbach Times, Publication (Box 5, Folder 45)
    By Crown Zellerbach Corp. Vol. 2, No. 10 October. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Crown Zellerbach Corp. Annual Report, Publication (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Item 10: Annual Report, Publication (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Item 11: Annual Report, Publication (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Item 12: Annual Report, Publication (Box 5, Folder 45)
- Box: 5, Folder: 46 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Item 1: Here it is! Good Ideas Mean Money for You: The Crucible Suggestion Plan, Publication (Box 5, Folder 46)
    By Crucible Steel. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Suggestion Plan Manual, Publication (Box 5, Folder 46)
- Box: 5, Folder: 47 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Item 1: People Come First, Publication (Box 5, Folder 47)
    By William F. Gutwein. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Group Insurance and Pension Plans for Employees and Their Dependents, Publication (Box 5, Folder 47)
    By C.T. Dearing Printing Company. Item is in English.
- Box: 5, Folder: 48 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Item 1: Your Ideas Can Be Worth Cash, Publication (Box 5, Folder 48)
    By Cudaly Packing Company. Item is in English.
- Box: 5, Folder: 49 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Item 1: Creative Artists Public Service Program, Publication (Box 5, Folder 49)
    By Cultural Council Foundation. Item is in English.
- Box: 5, Folder: 50 (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Item 1: Rules and Regulations of the Benefit Department, Publication (Box 5, Folder 50)
    By Curtis Lumber and Millwork Co. Item is in English.
- Box: 5, Folder: 51 (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Item 1: The New Look in Metallurgy, Publication (Box 5, Folder 51)
    By Curtiss-Wright Corp. May. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Agreement, Publication (Box 5, Folder 51)
    By Curtiss-Wright Corp. Sept. 18. Item is in English.
- Box: 5, Folder: 52 (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Item 1: Your Retirement Plan, Publication (Box 5, Folder 52)
    By Cutter Laboratories. Item is in English.
- Box: 5, Folder: 53 (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Item 1: "Let's Talk Shop", Publication (Box 5, Folder 53)
    By Cutler Hammer, Inc. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Company and You, Publication (Box 5, Folder 53)
    By Cutler Hammer, Inc. Sept. Item is in English.
- Box: 5, Folder: 54 (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Item 1: Successful Dairy Farmer I Have to be a Practical Man, Publication (Box 5, Folder 54)
    By Dairymen's League. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: A Milk Markeeting Organization Owned and Operated by and for Farmers, Publication (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Item 3: Dairymen's League News, Publication (Box 5, Folder 54)
    By Dairymen's League. Vol. 40, No. 18 Aug. 28. Item is in English.
- Box: 6, Folder: 1 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Annual Report, Publication (Box 6, Folder 1)
    By Dan River Mills, Inc. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Focus, Publication (Box 6, Folder 1)
    By Dan River Mills, Inc. Vol. 5, No. 2 March-April. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Suggestion Plan, Publication (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Annual Report, Publication (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: The Dan River Story, Publication (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Box: 6, Folder: 2 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: The Wrinkle is Dead, Publication (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: A Dictionary of Textile Terms, Publication (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: All About "Preset" Dan-Press, Publication (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: First in American Fabrics, Publication (Box 6, Folder 2)
    By Dan River Mills, Inc. 2 copies. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: A Brief History of Dan River, Publication (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Box: 6, Folder: 3 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: The Dan River Pattern, Publication (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Employee Handbook, Publication (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Opportunity at Dan River Mills for the College Man, Publication (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Information Sheet and conditions for Manuscript Use, Publication (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: Supervisor's Manual, Publication (Box 6, Folder 3)
    By Dan River Mills, Inc. 3/28. Item is in English.
- Box: 6, Folder: 4 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Safety Suggestions, Publication (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Your Dan River Pension Plan, Publication (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Group Medical Surgical Plan, Publication (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Group Life Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: Position Description: Clerical, Technical, and Supervisory Evaluaiton Plan, Publication (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: The Evaluation Plan and its Use, Publication (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Item 7: Summary of the Evaluation Plan for Clerical, Technical and Supervisory Positions, Publication (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Item 8: The Evaluation Plan and its Use, Publication (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Item 9: The Dan River Mills Profit Sharing Plan, Publication (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Item 10: Supervisory Training Program, Publication (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Item 11: Dean River Evening School Training Program, Publication (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Box: 6, Folder: 5 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Personal December Planning Calendar, Publication (Box 6, Folder 5)
    By Dartnell. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: 1972 Chart for Scheduling Vacations and Charting Absenteeism, Publication (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: Building an Effective and Acceptable Corporate Image, Publication (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: It's an Idea, Publication (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: How Kemper Insurance Office Produces Better Bulletin Boards, Publication (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: Here's an Idea!, Publication (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Item 7: An Error Becomes a Blunder When it's Repeated, Publication (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Item 8: Communications, Publication (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Item 9: Carelessness Can Foul Things Up, Publication (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Item 10: Help Flatten Waste, Publication (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Item 11: You Can Lose More Than an Argument!, Publication (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Item 12: The Three Blind Mice: Cut Off Their Tails With a Cost-Cutting Knife, Publication (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Item 13: Clerical Incentives: A Key to Reducing Office Costs, Publication (Box 6, Folder 5)
    By R.J. Little: W.L. Davidson. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Dartnell Survey of Sales Training Practices, Publication (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Item 15: Should You or Shouldn't You Engage a Consultant?, Publication (Box 6, Folder 5)
    By Richard J. Steele. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Successful Management Methods, Publication (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Item 17: What an Executive Should Know About Managing His Own Finances, Publication (Box 6, Folder 5)
    By Richard Frisbie. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: Year at a Glance Executive Planner, Publication (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Box: 6, Folder: 6 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Techniques for Spotting and Developing Employees Likely to Make Good Supervisory or Executive Material in Your Company, Publication (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: How to Select Better Salesmen, Executives, Office and S Employeesupervisory, Publication (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: Dartnell's New Personnel Administration Service, Publication (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: Personnel Adminstration: How the NLRB Applies New Jurisdictional Standards, Publication (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Item 5: Executive and Supervisory Development, Publication (Box 6, Folder 6)
    By Robert N. McMurry. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Methods Research in Management, Publication (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Item 7: Writing Letters to Employees' Homes, Publication (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Item 8: How Midland Cooperatives Administers its Salary Program in Executive and Supervisory Salary Levels, Publication (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Box: 6, Folder: 7 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Constitution and By-Laws, Publication (Box 6, Folder 7)
    By David Smith Steel Company. Item is in English.
- Box: 6, Folder: 8 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Your Life at davidson, Publication (Box 6, Folder 8)
    By Davidson Publishing Company. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Welcome to DPC, Publication (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Box: 6, Folder: 9 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: What it Means to be a Supervisor at Daystrom, Publication (Box 6, Folder 9)
    By Daystrom, Inc. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: National Defense Program Manpower Policies of Daystrom, Inc., Publication (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Item 3: Your Insurance, Publication (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Item 4: Employee Accident and Sickness Benefits, Publication (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Item 5: Your Incentive Play Plan, Publication (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Item 6: Why Job Evaluation?, Publication (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Box: 6, Folder: 10 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Agreement, Publication (Box 6, Folder 10)
    By Daystrom, Inc. Feb. 29 3 copies. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Agreement, Publication (Box 6, Folder 10)
    By Daystrom, Inc. March 12. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Agreement, Publication (Box 6, Folder 10)
    By Daystrom, Inc. April 19. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: By-Laws and Constitution, Publication (Box 6, Folder 10)
    By Daystrom, Inc. June. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: To All Hourly Employees, Publication (Box 6, Folder 10)
    By Daystrom, Inc. Feb. 20 1954. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Dear Fellow Employees, Publication (Box 6, Folder 10)
    By Daystrom, Inc. July 27. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: To Our Friends in the Community, Publication (Box 6, Folder 10)
    By Daystrom, Inc. Feb. 11. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Jan. 18, Publication (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Item 9: Letter, Publication (Box 6, Folder 10)
    By Daystrom, Inc. Feb. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Arbitration Award, Publication (Box 6, Folder 10)
    By Daystrom, Inc. Jan. 8. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Organization Chart, Publication (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Item 12: Strike Over, Two Plants Re-Open, Publication (Box 6, Folder 10)
    By Capital City News Bureau. March 8. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Union Calls at Daystrom Pickets, Publication (Box 6, Folder 10)
    By Capital City News Bureau. March 4. Item is in English.